baikalglobal.com 2010-05-15

# Privacy policy - London Stock Exchange

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

1.1 This Privacy Policy explains how Baikal Global Limited (“Baikal”, “we”, “us” or “our”) collects information from you when you visit or register to use [www.baikalglobal.com](http://www.baikalglobal.com/) (the “Website”) and how this information is then used. If you have any questions about this statement or your personal information that we may collect from you, please contact us at [enquiries@baikalglobal.com](mailto:enquiries@baikalglobal.com)

1.2 Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and re-visit this page from time to time to review any changes that may have been made.

1.3 We are registered as a data controller in accordance with United Kingdom Data Protection Act 1998. We will process any personal information we collect about you in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

1.4 This Privacy Policy applies to you whether you use the Website as a casual browser, have registered to use the Website or have entered into a contract with Baikal in relation to the supply of specific services and/or products. In the event of any conflict between this Privacy Policy and the terms of a contract you have with Baikal, the relevant provision of that contract shall prevail to the extent of any inconsistency.

**2\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES BAIKAL COLLECT, AND HOW IS THAT INFORMATION THEN USED?** 2.1 Information collected when you browse the Website

We will not collect any personal information about you from your browsing of the Website unless you agree to collection and use of your personal data.

2.2 Information collected when you become a customer of Baikal

When you enter into a contract with us for our services or products, you may be asked to submit personal information about yourself in order to receive or use these services or products. This information may include, for example, your name, address, job title, telephone number, email address and financial information necessary to conclude the contract and enable administration and management of such services or products. We will only collect information that is necessary for us to provide you with the product or service that you have requested. The type of information that we may collect will depend upon the nature of that service or product.

2.3 How will we use any personal information that we collect?

2.3.1 Where we collect personal information, we will use it for administration and to tailor our service and/or products to match your needs. We may also use personal information to conduct market research surveys, for statistical analysis to determine site usage, to run competitions and for direct marketing purposes relating to our business.

2.3.2 We may employ the services of a third party to help us in certain areas, such as website hosting, marketing and market researching. In some cases that third party may receive your information. However, at all times we will control and be responsible for the use of your information.

2.3.3 At all times we are legally obliged to collect, retain and process any personal information that you provide in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. Each time you provide us with personal information we aim to let you know how we intend to use it and ask you to give your consent to such use. This will include:

(a) where we would like to use that information to send you details of other products and services we offer which are similar to the product/service for which you have subscribed; and

(b) where we would like to share that information with certain selected third parties to allow them to provide you with details of their services and/or products which might be of interest to you.

2.4 How can I remove, update, prevent use of or correct my personal information?

Please refer to the “My Account” section of the Website, where you can update, correct or delete your personal information as appropriate. Should you wish Baikal to cease marketing to you, you should also utilise this area of the Website or contact enquiries@baikalglobal.com

**3\. HOW DOES BAIKAL PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?** 3.1 We will hold your personal information securely and will only keep it for as long as is reasonably necessary in the circumstances you are registered to use the Website or for as long as you use the service that you have requested, unless you have provided us with your consent to use the data for any additional purposes. We take the security of the Website and the information you provide very seriously and we will take all appropriate technical measures using recognized security procedures and tools in accordance with good industry practice to protect your personal information.

3.2 Whilst we use all reasonable endeavours to protect your security in the manner described above, we consider that it is only appropriate to advise users that data transmission over the Internet and the World Wide Web cannot always be guaranteed as 100% secure, and therefore that you use the Website at your own risk.

**4\. DOES BAIKAL USE COOKIES?** 4.1 Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the Website, in particular when you complete the “welcome form” on our homepage to indicate the user type which best describes you and also when you complete the “user poll”. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit most of the Website. A cookie does not provide us with any personal information. Therefore, if you have not supplied us with any personal information, you can still browse our site anonymously.

4.2 We do not automatically capture or store personal data from browsers to the site, other than to log your IP address and session information such as the duration of the visit to our site and the nature of the browser used. This information is used only for administration of the site system and in the compilation of statistics used by Baikal.

4.3 Cookies may be required to allow you to access and participate in certain areas of the Website. Once you have closed your browser, this type of cookie is deactivated.

4.4 Baikal also uses cookies when you complete the “welcome form” on our homepage to indicate the user type which best describes you. This cookie remains activated after you finish your current session and is used solely to enable us to provide content on our Website which is more relevant to you. Like all cookies, you are able to remove or block this particular cookie at any time (see 4.5 below).

4.5 Baikal also uses cookies when you complete the “user poll” on various pages across the Website. This cookie remains activated after you finish your current session and is used solely to show you the poll results once you have cast your vote. Like all cookies, you are able to remove or block this particular cookie at any time (see 4.6 below).

4.6 The majority of browsers will allow you to alter the settings used for cookies and to disable and enable them as you require. If you do not want cookies then please refer to the help menu on your browser for instructions on disabling them. For further general information on cookies and more detailed advice on how to disable and enable them please go to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org./>.

**5\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY** If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy these changes will be detailed on this page in order to ensure that you are fully aware of what information is collected, how it is used and under what circumstances it will be disclosed.

**6\. LINKS** This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by this Website. The Website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites and we would advise you to read the privacy statement of any website that collects personal information from you.
